I like this television very much.
我非常喜欢这台电视机.
How much does it cost?
请问它多少钱?
It's the most expensive model in the shop.
这是店里最贵的型号.
It costs five hundred pounds.
它的售价是500英镑.
That's too expensive for us.
这对我们来说太贵了.
We can't afford all that money.
我们花不起那么多钱.
This model's less expensive than that one.
这种型号比那种要便宜些.
It's only three hundred pounds.
它只要300英镑.
But, of course, it's not as good as the expensive one.
但是,它当然没有价钱高的那种好.
I don't like this model.
我不喜欢这种型号.
The other model's more expensive, but it's worth the money.
那种型号价格是贵一些,但它值这么多钱.
Can we buy it on instalments?
我们可以用分期付款的方式购买吗?
Of course. You can pay a deposit of thirty pounds,
当然可以.您可以先付30英镑定金.
and then fourteen pounds a month for three years.
然后每月14镑,3年付清.
Do you like it, dear?
你喜欢吗,亲爱的?
I certainly do, but I don't like the price.
我当然喜欢,但是我不喜欢这个价钱.
You always want the best, but we can't afford it.
你总是要买最好的,可我们买不起.
Sometimes you think you're a millionaire!
有时候你认为自己是个百万富翁!
Millionaires don't buy things on instalments!
百万富翁是不会分期付款买东西的!